hi welcome back to our alarm meditations
[Music]
we are kind of using it as a bullet
and especially the early times we were
all afraid we didn't know
is
during the difficult days
and then
that's called it's a stranger
let's say you're working i i used to
work in a company
we had a big company in new york
in all of their problems
even during this
of course
[Music]
is
and this is this is an act of truth
by that power
is
[Music]
just be here don't think about all the
stuff you have to do so
we all have stuff to do
[Music]
shoulders on the thighs
and we'll do 10 long exhales to get into
the meditation
so common
so please remember some kindness
during the time of the virus
now we're going to do an active tooth if
it's true yes
two people this is
[Music]
m
and may i be like him may i have my
music
[Music]
may i have this experience a meeting
my
here comes the big part of this
meditation yes come to help there it is
a meditation
if it's true i did do some small
kindness venezuela
[Music]
extreme
and libra and anonymously taking other
people's problems away from them
it was extreme sureness difficult
[Music]
my
this is a big universe this planet's not
the only place there is
cannot count them amazing wonderful
people
on many many
[Music]
um
b
these ideas are extremely unusual
you know these are concepts
much
is
[Music]
my
in the final verse um
and
okay and slowly open your eyes okay
take a good stretch okay we'll do this
meditation
foreign